

MIQDAM FERDIANSYAH HAMBALI

Software Engineer | Full-stack Developer | Web Developer

Birth Place : Bandung, Indonesia
Birth Date : 26 November 1999

Address : St. Belimbing II, Cimanggis, Depok, West Java, Indoenesia.

Mobile Number: +62 838-0583-9153



PROFILE

Begining of my journey in the programming world through the Indosat Ooredoo bootcamp in collaboration with Dicoding, specializing in web development and software development. Currently, I am pursuing my education at Nurul Fikri Integrated Technology College. With deep knowledge and skills in programming, I have been continuously improving my expertise over the past two years as a software engineer.

I expertise, passionate, and driven in software engineer with a strong foundation both back-end and front-end. Dedicated to contribute my expertise to a forward-thinking team, while continuously learning and growing in the ever-evolving world of technology.

A

EXPERIENCE

- Assistant technician PT. Varley vendor Indonesia Power PLTU JABAR 2, Pelabuhanratu, Sukabumi, Indonesia. (Non IT)
 August 2021 - November 2021
- Activity College Projects Software Developer at Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri.
 October 2022 - Present
- Software Engineer freelancer as Full-stack Developer (Self employed)
 December 2022 - Present
- Web Developer Internship at GAOTek Inc. Jakarta, Indonesia. (Remote)
 April 2024 - Present



SKILL

- Programing Languages :
 - XML, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Type Script, & PHP. (Advance Level)
 - Dart, Python, Java. (Knowledge Intermediate)

Stack :

- React JS, Next JS, Node JS, Express JS, Nest JS, Laravel, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Supabase, Firebase, Bootstrap, & Tailwind. (Advance Level)
- React Native, Flutter, Angular JS, GraphQL, AWS, GCP, & MongoDB. (Knowledge)



EDUCATION

- Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri Depok, Indonesia
 Bachelor Degree of Computer Science
 2022 - Present
- Sootcamp Indosat x Dicoding Web & Software Developer 2022
- PKBM Bakti Nusa Bogor, Jawa Barat Home Schooling (Non Formal) 2021-2022
- SMAN 01 Palabuhanratu, Sukabumi Senior High School (Social Science) 2017- 2019

CONTACT

- LinkedIn:
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/miqdamhambali
- Fmail
- <u>miqd22166ti@student.nurulfik</u>ri.ac.id
- _ Website:
- https://miqdam-hambali.vercel.app
 - Github:
- https://github.com/maymiquy